I Come with the Rain is a thriller, mystery film directed by Trần Anh Hùng.
Kline, a former Los Angeles police officer turned private detective, is hired by a powerful pharmaceutical conglomerate boss to
investigate in Asia the disappearance of his only son, Shitao, whom he has not seen in person since the boy was ten.
Now in his 30s, Shitao has gone missing in the Philippines
where he had been helping in an orphanage.
Kline, played by Josh Hartnett.
Hasford, played by Elias Koteas.
Shitao, played by Takuya Kimura.
Su Dongpo, played by Lee Byung-hun.
Lili, played by Trần Nữ Yên Khê.
Meng Zi, played by Shawn Yue.
I Come with the Rain is a 2009 neo-noir thriller written and directed by Vietnamese-born
French director Tran Anh Hung, starring American actor Josh Hartnett.
After making three movies about Vietnam, Hung intended to make a baroque action film, a passionate thriller, both intense and poetic, haunted by
three characters from the mythology of film and the Western world: the serial killer, the private investigator, and the Christ figure.
The film takes place in Los Angeles, Mindanao and Hong Kong
and brings together American and Asian actors.
The film score was written by the Argentine Academy Award winner Gustavo
Santaolalla and the English alternative rock band Radiohead.
The film also made heavy use of post-rock music, including
songs by Explosions in the Sky, Godspeed You!
Black Emperor, and A Silver Mt.
The film premiered in Tokyo at Toho Cinemas Roppongi Hills on 27 May 2009.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.